

# TIRTA STYADI

## WEB DEVELOPER STUDENT / PROFESSIONAL PASTRY CHEF

+61 451 933 855

55

tirta.setiady@yahoo.com

#### **ABOUT ME**

Over 6 Years since I came to Australia I work as Professional Pastry Chef, but before that I was working as Graphic Designer for Garuda Maintenance Facility also freelancer for few company and individual purposes.

I am thinking to switch my career to become web developer or software developer that is my biggest motivation and that is why at the moment I am studying web developer at University of Sydney Coding Bootcamp to improve my knowledge and experience.

#### LANGUAGES & TECH

Python JavaScript Node.Js HTML CSS

Adobe Photoshop Adobe Premiere Adobe Illustrator

### CERTIFICATION

Python Short Course ( Udemy )

Advance Diploma of Hospitality

Certificate IV in Patisserie

Advance Diploma Of Accounting

Bachelor of Design and Visual Communication

#### **WORK EXPERIENCES**

Pastry Chef de Partie, Maggio's, Cammeray August 2020 - Present

Main duty to take care of production pastries and cake also make sure everything based on standard, developed menu.

#### Pastry Chef de Partie, Blackstar Pastry, Sydney

November 2017 - August 2020

Main duty to take care of production pastries and cake also make sure everything based on standard, also developed menu and working closely with apprentice and commis chef.

#### Pastry Chef, Wholegrain Bakery, Sydney

June 2017 - November 2017

Main duty to take ca re of production pastries and cake also make sure everything based on standard, working closely with apprentice and commis chef.

#### Pastry Chef, Central Baking Depot (CBD), Sydney

January 2017 - June 2017

Main duty to take care of production pastries and cake also make sure everything based on standard.

### Pastry Chef, St Malo Bakery, Hornsby

September 2014 - December 2016

Main duty to take care of production pastries and cake also make sure everything based on standard, working closely with apprentice and commis chef.



April 2014 - August 2014

Main duty as a baker make bread or specialist in American Bagel

#### Freelancer Graphic Designer

July 2013 - January 2014

Freelance Graphic Designer. Most works apply to advertising.

#### Garuda Maintenance Facilities

January 2013 - June 2013

Graphic Designer, help them to design the instruction book for Boeing 777 - 300ER

#### **EDUCATION**

Advance Diploma Of Hospitality Management, Sydney Business and Travel Academy

January 2018 - April 2019

Certificate IV if Patisserie, William Angliss Institute

July 2016 - December 2017

Advance Diploma Of Accounting, Macquarie Institute

May 2014 - May 2016

Bachelor of Design and Visual Communication at University Of Bunda Mulia, Jakarta

May 2014 - May 2016